<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Map -->
    <string name="map_btn_start">Start</string>
    <string name="map_btn_done">Finish</string>
    <string name="map_crosshair">Map crosshair</string>
    <string name="map_label_lat">Latitude</string>
    <string name="map_label_long">Longitude</string>
    <string name="map_label_zoom">Zoom</string>
    <string name="map_label_time">Time</string>
    <string name="map_default_value">--</string>
    <string name="map_default_time">--:--:---</string>

    <!-- Start -->
    <string name="start_title">Start</string>
    <string name="start_run_experiment">Run Experiment</string>
    <string name="start_demo_touch">Demo Touch</string>
    <string name="start_demo_face">Demo Facial Tracking</string>
    <string name="start_help">Instructions</string>
    <string name="start_cleanup_data">Cleanup Data</string>
    <string name="start_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="start_clean_message">Delete data directory and all its content?</string>
    <string name="start_clean_ok">Yes</string>
    <string name="start_clean_cancel">No</string>

    <!-- Setup -->
    <string name="setup_title">Setup</string>
    <string name="setup_experiment_title">Experiment</string>
    <string name="setup_btn_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="setup_btn_reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="setup_btn_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="setup_user_initials">User initials:</string>
    <string name="setup_part">Participant code:</string>
    <string name="setup_group">Group code:</string>
    <string name="setup_trials">Number of trials per mode:</string>
    <string name="setup_orders_title">Ordering</string>
    <string name="setup_logging_title">Logging</string>
    <string name="setup_logging_data_directory">Data directory:</string>
    <string name="setup_logging_data_file">Data output file:</string>

    <!-- Results -->
    <string name="results_title">Results</string>
    <string name="results_thanks">Thank You</string>
    <string name="results_btn_email">Email</string>
    <string name="results_btn_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="results_text_1">
        You have completed the user study.
        Tap the Email button below to send the data file created.
        If fails or not possible, email the file at:	</string>
    <string name="results_text_2">to:</string>
    <string name="results_text_3">
        Do not delete any created data files until after
        you have received confirmation from the author.	</string>
    <string name="results_text_4">
        Please also complete the survey regarding your user feedback
        for this experiment at the following URL:	</string>

    <!-- Help -->
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
	<string name="help_btn_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="help_text_1">
        This application is intended for a user study to
        examine the differences between touch-based input and
        facial-tracking. 
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_2">    
        The test will occur in a quiet room with favourable lighting
        conditions where the participants will be seated at a table.
        The Experiment mode will run a certain number of trials (default
        of 5) with one input method and then the same number of trials
        with the other method. In each trial, a random point on the
        map is selected (marked by the pin). The marker will always be
        placed in the field of view at the start of each trial.
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_3">
        In touch mode, the user must press the Start button to
        begin. To goal is to center the pin, while zooming until
        the indicated zoom difference is 0.0 (in the status bar).
        A crosshair will be provided to help the user center the marker.
        The crosshair should be centered at the bottom tip of the pin, 
        not the center of the pin. The user may pan the map by swiping 
        left, right, up and down with one finger, and zoom in and out
        with two-finger pitch. Please do not use the double tap gesture
        to focus and zoom.
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_4">
        For the facial tracking mode, participants will be instructed
        to keep their hands and forearms on the table to ensure that
        the device does not move. The device will be tilted back slightly
        such that the participant\'s face is centered in the camera\'s field
        of view. User\'s face should be a distance of about 30 cm away from
        the screen to start. The user must remain still for 5 seconds before
        each trial begins. Moving one\'s head toward and away from the screen
        will zoom in and out respectively. Moving one\'s head side-to-side or
        tilting one\'s head left and right will pan the map west and east
        respectively. And Moving one\'s head up and down or tilting one\'s 
        head up and down will pan the map north and south respectively. An
        indicator, will display the preceived location of the left and right
        eyes, the zoom difference as well as the direction to the target when
        outside of the field of view. Zoom difference of +/- 0.5 is acceptable.
        Centering is based on the focus between the eyes or the center of the
        screen.
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_5">
    	A status bar at the bottom of the screen will indicate the
        difference in latitude, longitude and zoom from the desired target
        as well as the time elapsed. You will hear an audio tone to start and
        when you finish. Each trial is run for a maximum of 5 minutes, at which
        time the trial will time out. Press the "Finish" or "Timed Out" button
        to continue to the next trial.
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_6">
    	For a demonstration, try the Demo Touch or Demo Facial Tracking modes.
    	For further clarification, feel free to email: 
    </string>

</resources>
